<resources>
    <string name="app_name">DilPay</string>

    <string name="about1">About DilPay</string>
    <string name="about2">DilPay is India’s Best online bus ticketing and recharge bill payments platform that has transformed  bus ticket bill payments by bringing with new idea of benefiting users with each payments transaction ,we are happy to say DilPay is the next biggest evaluation in online business.Founded in 2019 with great idea of unmatched benefits on your every transaction.</string>
    <string name="about3">Why Choose Us</string>
    <string name="about4">We provide better service. Give you best offers on your transactions. We Definitly make you feel happy and satisfy about your usage of our service.</string>
    <string name="about5">Our Mission</string>
    <string name="about6">Aim to make DilPay, Based on customer view best price and beautiful experience and based on our view best service</string>

    <string name="contact1">Get In Touch</string>
    <string name="contact2">For Customer Support and Query, Get in touch with us: Help</string>
    <string name="contact3">DilPay Services India Pvt.Ltd.</string>
    <string name="contact4">H.no : 3-4-104/1,</string>
    <string name="contact5">Narsimha Nagar Colony,</string>
    <string name="contact6">Mallapur X Road,</string>
    <string name="contact7">Near Shiva Hotel,</string>
    <string name="contact8">Hyderabad Rangareddy-500074,</string>
    <string name="contact9">Telangana</string>
    <string name="contact10">Telephone</string>
    <string name="contact11">(+91)9059143346</string>
    <string name="contact12">Business Inquiries</string>
    <string name="contact13">support@dilpay.in</string>

    <string name="faq1">Get answers to your queries</string>
    <string name="faq2">Online payments with Dilpay application.</string>
    <string name="qn1">How can I Recharge Mobile and DTH?.</string>
    <string name="ans1">You can recharge your mobile by opening Dilpay application then select mobile on displayed options and choose your recharge type like Prepaid or Postpaid then enter your mobile number on the given field and select your operator then enter amount for your recharge or if you want to browse plans, just click on View Plans option and select your plan and click on next button then provide your payment details like card details or UPI details for recharge your mobile after providing required information just click on Payment button so your payment processed. If you want to recharge your DTH Service on the given field select your operator, on next filed enter your card number then enter amount for your recharge or if you want to browse plans, just click on View Plans option and select your plan and click on next button then provide your payment details like card details or UPI details for recharge your DTH service after providing required information just click on Payment button so your payment processed same like this you can do Datacard Recharge, Cable Tv Recharge, LandLine Recharge which is a very simple three step process. We advise you to check all the details you entered once before proceed to payment. </string>
    <string name="qn2">What happens when my transaction cancelled?</string>
    <string name="ans2">Dont worry about your transaction cancelled issue. some times the transactions may be cancelled by Server Response Problems, Incorrect Transaction Details, Operator Related Issues.If any money from your account is deducted for failure transactions you dont need to worry as soon as possible we resolve your problem by refunding your deducted amount or else make your transaction successful. We will make every effort to ensure that increase success rate of your transaction.</string>
    <string name="qn3">How can I do Bill Payments?.</string>
    <string name="ans3">Dilpay application providing you the one portal for all transactional services. Using Dilpay application You can pay your Electricity Bill, Water Bill, Gas Bill Etc., For EX: If you want to pay your Electricity Bill, open Dilpay application.in then select Electricity on displayed options in that select your Operator from given list, on the next filed select your state then enter your service number and on the next field enter amount and click on next button then provide your payment details like card details or UPI details for doing your Bill-Payment after providing required information just click on Payment button so your payment processed like this you can proceed to do all your Bill-Payments by Dilpay application with 100% success rate and secure and easy process.</string>
    <string name="qn4">What is your Refer and Earn Concept</string>
    <string name="ans4">Yeah.. its Quite difficult to understand but it works extraordinary. Our Main Concept is Dilpay application have to beneficial for all its customers who uses our services so for that we implemented a amazing Algorithm which works on the concept of do transaction on Dilpay application and benefit your self as well as your near Dilpay customers, So the reward will be like cash back and shared to you and your surround Dilpay customers
        \n  FOR EX: if you do any successful transaction on Dilpay application the cash back will be credited to you and your neighbours who use Dilpay application like that if anyone near you do successful payment then the cash back will credits to you also, if you are a Dilpay customer, the number transaction done by near you so the cash back credited to you on every transaction like that every Dilpay customer will get beneficial.</string>
    <string name="qn5">Is Cash back is Awarded every time?</string>
    <string name="ans5">Yes Obviously! You can get cash back on every transaction you do and also cash back will credited to your account by if someone near you done a transaction.</string>
    <string name="qn6">Is Dilpay application Secure for Online Transactions?</string>
    <string name="ans6">Dilpay application uses very secure payment gateway and with 100% successful transaction ratio. So you don,t need to worry about transactions on Dilpay application.</string>
    <string name="qn7">Is this Services will applicable to all States in India ?</string>
    <string name="ans7">No. At present we are launching these services to Telangana only. Although we have planed to provide this services to all States in India but it take some time.</string>
    <string name="qn8">Did all services from Dilpay application will give Cash back?.</string>
    <string name="ans8">Yes. Dilpay application will give you Cash back on all the payments services which we provide.</string>
    <string name="qn9">Is it mandatory to create an account in Dilpay application?.</string>
    <string name="ans9">Yes. Without Account you cant proceed to do any transaction.</string>
    <string name="qn10">Is My data secure in Dilpay application?.</string>
    <string name="ans10">Dilpay application will assure you about safety of your information. Dilpay application will not misuse your information. We use your information for your online transactions purpose only.</string>


    <string name="pol1">Type of information we collect and its legal basis</string>
    <string name="pol000">4.By downloading/using/accessing the Dilpay application indicate that you understand, agree and consent to this privacy policy.The Dilpay app is fully designed for business and/or personal use purposes, A user hereby provide your unconditional consent or agreements to the Dilpay</string>
    <string name="pol2">The information as detailed below is collected for us to be able to provide the services chosen by you and also to fulfill our legal obligations as well as our obligations towards third parties as per our User Agreement.</string>
    <string name="pol3">"Personal Information" of User shall include the information shared by the User and collected by us for the following purposes:</string>
    <string name="pol4"> Information which you provide while subscribing to or registering on the Website, including but not limited to information about your personal identity such as name, gender, age etc., your contact details such as your email address, postal addresses, telephone (mobile or otherwise) and/or fax numbers. The information may also include information such as your banking details (including credit/debit card) and any other information relating to your income and/or lifestyle; billing information payment history etc. (as shared by you).</string>
    <string name="pol5"> We many also collect some other information and documents including but not limited to:</string>
    <string name="pol6">1.Transactional history (other than banking details) about your e-commerce activities, buying behavior.</string>
    <string name="pol7">2.Your user names, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services.</string>
    <string name="pol8">3.Data either created by you or by a third party and which you wish to store on our servers such as image files, documents etc.</string>
    <string name="pol001">6."Business Partners" – Shall refer to any individual, group of individuals defined under law with whom Dilpay have a contractual relationship not limited to Merchants, Advertisers, Deal partners, Financial institutions.</string>
    <string name="pol002">7."Service Providers" – Refers to any individual, group of individuals defined under law whose services are used by Dilpay in order to provide the intended services to You through Dilpay platforms.</string>
    <string name="pol10">5.Information pertaining any other user(s) for who you make a transaction for(booking, recharge, etc.,) through your registered Dilpay account. In such case, you must confirm and represent that each of the other user(s) for whom a booking or payment has been made, has agreed to have the information shared by you disclosed to us and further be shared by us with the concerned service provider(s).</string>
    <string name="pol11">How we use your personel information</string>
    <string name="pol12">The Personal Information collected maybe used in the following manner:</string>
    <string name="pol13">1.While making a transaction:</string>
    <string name="pol14">While making a transaction, we may use Personal Information including, payment details which include cardholder name, credit/debit card number (in encrypted form) with expiration date, banking details, wallet details etc. as shared and allowed to be stored by you. We may also use the information of travelers list as available in or linked with your account. This information is presented to the User at the time of making a payment to enable you to complete your transaction expeditiously.</string>
    <string name="pol15">2.We may also use your Personal Information for several reasons including but not limited to:</string>
    <string name="pol16">1.keep you informed of the transaction status;</string>
    <string name="pol17">2.Your usernames, passwords, email addresses and other security-related information used by you in relation to our Services.</string>
    <string name="pol18">3.send payment or transaction confirmations either via SMS or notification format or any other messaging service.</string>
    <string name="pol19">4.send any updates or status of your transaction(s).</string>
    <string name="pol20">5.allow our customer service to contact you, if necessary.</string>
    <string name="pol21">6.customize the content of our website, mobile site and mobile app.</string>
    <string name="pol22">7.request for reviews of products or services or any other improvements.</string>
    <string name="pol23">8.send verification message(s) or email(s).</string>
    <string name="pol24">9.Validate/authenticate your account and to prevent any misuse or abuse.</string>
    <string name="pol25">3.Survey:</string>
    <string name="pol26">We value opinions and comments from our Users and frequently conduct surveys, both online and offline. Participation in these surveys is entirely optional. Typically, the information received is aggregated, and used to make improvements to Application, other Sales Channels, services and to develop appealing content, features and promotions for members based on the results of the surveys. Identity of the survey participants is anonymous unless otherwise stated in the survey.</string>
    <string name="pol27">How long do we keep your personal information?</string>
    <string name="pol28">Dilpay will retain your Personal Information on its servers for as long as is reasonably necessary for the purposes listed in this policy. In some circumstances we may retain your Personal Information for longer periods of time, for instance where we are required to do so in accordance with any legal, regulatory, tax or accounting requirements.</string>
    <string name="pol29">With whom your personal information is shared</string>
    <string name="pol30">1.Service Providers and suppliers:</string>
    <string name="pol31">Your information shall be shared with the end service providers like hotels, bus service providers, cab rental or any other suppliers who are responsible for fulfilling your payment transactions. You may note that while making a booking, or bill payment with Dilpay you authorize us to share your information with the said service providers and suppliers. It is pertinent to note that Dilpay does not authorize the end service provider to use your information for any other purpose(s) except as may be for fulfilling their part of service. However, how the said service providers/suppliers use the information shared with them is beyond the purview and control of Dilpay as they process Personal Information as independent data controllers, and hence we cannot be made accountable for the same. You are therefore advised to review the privacy policies of the respective service provider or supplier whose services you choose to avail.</string>
    <string name="pol32">Dilpay does not sell or rent individual customer names or other Personal Information of Users to third parties except sharing of such information with our business / alliance partners or vendors who are engaged by us for providing various referral services and for sharing promotional and other benefits to our customers from time to time basis their booking history with us.</string>
    <string name="pol33">2.Companies in the same group :</string>
    <string name="pol34">In the interests of improving personalization and service efficiency, we may, under controlled and secure circumstances, share your Personal Information with our affiliate or associate entities.</string>
    <string name="pol35">If the assets of Dilpay are acquired, our customer information may also be transferred to the acquirer depending upon the nature of such acquisition. In addition, as part of business expansion/development/restructuring or for any other reason whatsoever, if we decide to sell/transfer/assign our business, any part thereof, any of our subsidiaries or any business units, then as part of such restructuring exercise customer information including the Personal Information collected herein shall be transferred accordingly.</string>
    <string name="pol36">3.Business partners and third-party vendors</string>
    <string name="pol37">We may also share certain filtered Personal Information to our corporate affiliates or business partners who may contact the customers to offer certain products or services, which may include free or paid products / services, which will enable the customer to have better travel experience or to avail certain benefits specially made for Dilpay customers. Examples of such partners are entities offering co-branded credit cards, travel insurance, insurance cover against loss of wallet, banking cards or similar sensitive information etc. If you choose to avail any such services offered by our business partners, the services so availed will be governed by the privacy policy of the respective service provider.</string>
    <string name="pol38">Dilpay may share your Personal Information to third party that Dilpay may engage to perform certain tasks on its behalf, including but not limited to payment processing, data hosting, and data processing platforms.</string>
    <string name="pol39">We use non-identifiable Personal Information of Users in aggregate or anonymized form to build higher quality, more useful online services by performing statistical analysis of the collective characteristics and behavior of our customers and visitors, and by measuring demographics and interests regarding specific areas of the Website. We may provide anonymous statistical information based on this data to suppliers, advertisers, affiliates and other current and potential business partners. We may also use such aggregate data to inform these third parties as to the number of people who have seen and clicked on links to their websites. Any Personal Information which we collect and which we may use in an aggregated format is our property. We may use it, in our sole discretion and without any compensation to you, for any legitimate purpose including without limitation the commercial sale thereof to third parties.</string>
    <string name="pol40">Occasionally, Dilpay application will hire a third party for market research, surveys etc. and will provide information to these third parties specifically for use in connection with these projects. The information (including aggregate cookie and tracking information) we provide to such third parties, alliance partners, or vendors are protected by confidentiality agreements and such information is to be used solely for completing the specific project, and in compliance with the applicable regulations.</string>
    <string name="pol41">4.Disclosure of information</string>
    <string name="pol42">In addition to the circumstances described above, Dilpay application may disclose Users Personal Information if required to do so:</string>
    <string name="pol43">1.by law, required by any enforcement authority for investigation, by court order or in reference to any legal process.</string>
    <string name="pol44">2.to conduct our business;</string>
    <string name="pol45">3.for regulatory, internal compliance and audit exercise(s)</string>
    <string name="pol46">4.to secure our systems; or</string>
    <string name="pol47">to enforce or protect our rights or properties of Dilpay or any or all of its affiliates, associates, employees, directors or officers or when we have reason to believe that disclosing Personal Information of User(s) is necessary to identify, contact or bring legal action against someone who may be causing interference with our rights or properties, whether intentionally or otherwise, or when anyone else could be harmed by such activities.
Such disclosure and storage may take place without your knowledge. In that case, we shall not be liable to you or any third party for any damages howsoever arising from such disclosure and storage.</string>
    <string name="pol48">How we protect your personal information?</string>
    <string name="pol49">All payments on the Website are secured. This means all Personal Information you provide is transmitted using TLS (Transport Layer Security) encryption. TLS is a proven coding system that lets your browser automatically encrypt, or scramble, data before you send it to us. Website has stringent security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information under our control. Whenever you change or access your account information, we offer the use of a secure server. Once your information is in our possession we adhere to strict security guidelines, protecting it against unauthorized access.</string>
    <string name="pol50">Changes to the privacy policy</string>
    <string name="pol51">You must at least 18 years of age to transact directly with Dilpay and also to consent to the processing of your personal data.</string>
    <string name="pol52">1.Registration on the Application:</string>
    <string name="pol53">2.Other information:</string>


    <string name="terms1">General Terms And Conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms2">1.<b>DilPay Application from  (DilPay Services India Pvt. Ltd.)</b> is an aggregator for online bus ticketing inventory and Bill payments and Recharge Service Provider. DilPay enables travellers to book bus tickets online right from the comfort of their home or office by providing them with choice of bus operators, departure times and prices. DilPay does not own or operate any bus services on its own. DilPay does not advice any specific bus operator to its customers. The choice of the bus operator is purely the discretion of the customer.</string>
    <string name="terms3">2.The arrival and departure times mentioned on the ticket are only tentative timings. Buses may be delayed due to some unavoidable reasons like traffic jams etc. However, the bus will not leave the source before the time that is mentioned on the ticket. Passengers are advised to call the bus operator contact number mentioned in the ticket and reconfirm the boarding point location and departure time on the day of journey.</string>
    <string name="terms4">3.Passengers are required to furnish the following details at the time of boarding the bus. Failing to do so, they may not be allowed to board the bus.</string>
    <string name="terms5">3.1. SMS of the ticket or Email. (This is widely accepted by most bus operators)</string>
    <string name="terms6">3.2. Some operators do not accept the electronic ticket formats. We provide the details of such operators while booking tickets on DilPay App. In such case we request you to kindly carry a printout of the ticket.</string>
    <string name="terms7">3.3. Proof of Identity (Driving License or Aadhar Card or Passport or PAN Card or Voter Card)</string>
    <string name="terms8">4.The passengers should reach at the mentioned boarding points 15 minutes prior to the scheduled departure time.</string>
    <string name="terms9">5.A booking is considered confirmed if the booking confirmation page is shown to the customer, even if SMS/Email fails to deliver for any reason.</string>
    <string name="terms10">6.<b>dilpay.in</b> provides a platform to Insurance company to list and Advertise their services on the website and App and allows customers You (Customer/You) to select Insurance Policy, based on your preferences. The listing of an Insurance Policy on the website does not constitute and should not be regarded as a recommendation. Once a reservation is made, and Insurance policy is selected You are agreeing to the terms and conditions of the Insurance Company.</string>
    <string name="terms11">7.DilPay Ultimate and Assured classification of Bus Operators is done from time-to-time based on Customers Feedback and Surveys conducted by DilPay. DilPay is showing the classification for customers to make an informed decision while choosing a Bus Operator for their journey. The choice of the bus operator is purely at the discretion of the customer. The classification of Bus Operator might change depending on the service performance of bus operator.</string>
    <string name="terms12">8.If ticket confirmation/cancellation, SMS/Email, is not sent for any reason, if reported it can be resent by our support team. SMS/Email might fail to deliver or get delayed for several reasons which are not in DilPay control.</string>
    <string name="terms13">9.Payment gateway/service charges DilPay will not charge any additional payment gateway charge or service unless otherwise specified in the booking details page.</string>
    <string name="terms14">10.Any complaints/grievances should be reported in a weeks time from date of journey performed.</string>
    <string name="terms15">11.By making a booking on dilpay.in customer acknowledges that DilPay will Call/Email/SMS or send alerts to give/take information regarding his/her bookings.</string>
    <string name="terms16">12.In case of any claims arising out of unforeseen consequences/exigencies, DilPay liability would be limited to the extent of two times the value of the booking amount.</string>
    <string name="terms17">13.The terms and conditions of our services can be amended, modified or withdrawn by dilpay.in at any time without notice.</string>
    <string name="terms18">14.All legal disputes are subject to exclusive jurisdiction of the competent courts in Hyderabad (Telangana) only.</string>
    <string name="terms19">Offers and Discounts</string>
    <string name="terms20">1.No two offers that are live can be combined to be redeemed.</string>
    <string name="terms21">2.Any offer published by DilPay or its partners can be changed without prior notice.</string>
    <string name="terms22">3.Each offer can have its own terms and conditions. Please refer to the offers page.</string>
    <string name="terms23">Our Responsibilities</string>
    <string name="terms24">1.Generation of a valid bus ticket through its partners/operators.</string>
    <string name="terms25">2.Sending an SMS, Email for ticket confirmation/cancellation.</string>
    <string name="terms26">3.Providing voice/email support for any ticket booking/cancellation/refund issues</string>
    <string name="terms27">Not Our Responsibilities</string>
    <string name="terms28">1.Any incorrect data provided by customer while booking the ticket.</string>
    <string name="terms29">2.Any Bus delays, breakdowns, service cancellations and accidents.</string>
    <string name="terms30">3.Any misbehaviour by the operator staff or co-passenger.</string>
    <string name="terms31">4.Loss/damage of baggage.</string>
    <string name="terms32">5.Late arrival by customer at the boarding point.</string>
    <string name="terms33">6.Customer phone not reachable, operator did not call at the boarding point and left without picking the customer.</string>
    <string name="terms34">7.Customer waiting at wrong boarding point.</string>
    <string name="terms35">8.Any change of seat numbers done by the bus operator manually.</string>
    <string name="terms36">9.Operator changing the boarding point for any reason.</string>
    <string name="terms37">10.Operator arranging a different vehicle for pickup at boarding point and boarding the actual vehicle at a different place.</string>
    <string name="terms38">11.Operator objecting on carrying pets.</string>
    <string name="terms39">12.Improper booking done by agent, please contact the agent directly.</string>
    <string name="terms40">13.Operator not providing In bus amenities/facilities mentioned while booking.</string>
    <string name="terms41">14.Change of bus type by Bus operator for any reason.</string>
    <string name="terms42">15.Bus fares are not controlled by DilPay, so any change in fares is not the responsibility of DilPay.</string>
    <string name="terms43">16.The fare might vary based on the seat selected. So the fare shown in the Search Page and seat Selection Page might vary. For Govt. Bus Operators Bookings, Total fare is calculated as per the Govt. Rules after entering the passenger age.</string>
    <string name="terms44">17.The rules and regulations for carrying luggages vary among bus operators. Most of the operators allow 15-/20 Kgs of luggage (Bags, Suitcases) per passenger. Bus Operator has sole discretion to allow passengers to carry any other form of luggages like carton boxes etc. DilPay is not responsible in case passenger is not allowed to board the bus if the luggage is inappropriate (valuable goods, explosives, carton boxes etc) to carry in the bus. Please check with bus operator directly in case any extra luggage/carton boxes etc are being carried</string>
    <string name="terms45">User Accounts</string>
    <string name="terms46">DilPay may offer You the facility of opening user account on the app. This user account can be linked to the Your phone number or email-id or both. For Your use of the app, either by registering an account with DilPay, You agree to the following:</string>
    <string name="terms47">1.You are solely responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of Your account and password and for restricting access to Your device to prevent unauthorized access to Your account when You use the app by registering an account with DilPay.</string>
    <string name="terms48">2.By using the app, either as registered user, You authorize DilPay and its agents to access third party sites, including but not limited to that of banks and other payment gateways, designated by the bank or on the banks behalf for retrieving requested information for processing of a customer generated transaction on the app.</string>
    <string name="terms49">3.In the event that You use the app through a registered account, You agree to accept responsibility for all activities that occur through your DilPay account.</string>
    <string name="terms50">4.In the event that You use the Website through a registered account, You should take all necessary steps to ensure that the password is kept confidential and secure and should inform DilPay immediately if You have any reason to believe that Your password has been compromised, or if the password is being, or is likely to be, used in an unauthorized manner. DilPay shall not be liable for any losses You may incur owing to any compromised login credentials of Your DilPay account. Please ensure that the details You provide DilPay are correct, complete and up to date and inform DilPay immediately of any changes to the information that You provide at the time of registering Your account with DilPay.</string>
    <string name="terms51">5.DilPay will not be responsible for screening, censoring or otherwise controlling transactions, including ascertaining whether the transaction is legal and valid as per the laws of the land, if you are resident/national of a country other than India.</string>
    <string name="terms52">6.You warrant that You will abide by all such additional procedures and guidelines, as modified from time to time, in connection with Your use of Our services. You shall also be liable to comply with all applicable laws and regulations regarding use of the app with respect to the jurisdiction concerned for each transaction.</string>
    <string name="terms53">7.app may be used for Your personal and non-commercial purposes only. Therefore, You are not allowed to re-sell, deep-link, use, copy, monitor (e.g. spider, scrape), display, download or reproduce any content or information, software, products or Facility available on app for any commercial or competitive activity/purpose.</string>
    <string name="terms54">8.DilPay reserves the right to refuse Your access to app, terminate Your DilPay account, cancel any bus ticket reservations, remove and/or edit content on the app at any time without notice if we have reasonable belief that Your account is being used for purposes other than as defined under Clause 3(7).</string>
    <string name="terms55">9.Use of the app is available only to persons who can enter into legally binding contracts under the applicable law. Persons who are "incompetent to contract" within the meaning of the applicable law are not eligible to use the app. If You are a minor, you shall not register as a User of the app and shall not transact on or use the app.</string>
    <string name="terms56">10.As a minor if You wish to use or transact on the app, such use or transaction may be made by Your legal guardian or parents. We reserve the right to terminate Your membership and/or refuse to provide You with access to the app if it is discovered that You are a minor or incompetent to contract according to the law.</string>
    <string name="terms57">Failure Transactions</string>
    <string name="terms58">1.A transaction might fail for several reasons and your account/card might be debited without generating a ticket. If the amount is deducted from your account/card, we request you to call our customer care number to re-confirm the failed transaction before proceeding with a fresh transaction/booking.</string>
    <string name="terms59">2.Transactions such as these are refunded back to customer. Please read the refund policy below..</string>
    <string name="terms60">Miscellaneous</string>
    <string name="terms61">1.The Parties acknowledge and accept that electronic format shall be deemed an acceptable means of communication for the purposes of these Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms62">2.These Terms constitute the complete and entire set of terms between the Parties on the subject of terms of usage of the Website (save and except the other policies and terms referred to in these Terms) and shall supersede any and all other prior understandings, commitments, representations or agreements, whether written or oral, between the Parties to these Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms63">3.If any provision of these Terms shall be found by any court or administrative body of competent jurisdiction to be invalid or unenforceable, such invalidity or enforceability shall not affect the other provisions of these Terms, which shall remain in full force and effect.</string>
    <string name="terms64">4.In no event will any delay, failure or omission (in whole or in part) in enforcing, exercising or pursuing any right, power, privilege, claim or remedy conferred by or arising under these Terms or by law, be deemed to be or construed as a waiver of that or any other right, so as to bar the enforcement of that, or any other right, power privilege, claim or remedy, in any other instance at any time or times subsequently.</string>
    <string name="terms65">Limitation Of Liability</string>
    <string name="terms66">The website/DilPay will not be liable for any damages of any kind, including without limitation, direct, indirect, incidental, punitive, and consequential damages, arising out of or in connection with the terms, site, facility, transaction processing service, inability to use the facility or the transaction processing service, or those resulting from any facility purchased or obtained or messages received or transactions entered into through the website, beyond the value of the last transaction carried out by you through the website</string>
    <string name="terms67">Cancellation policy.</string>
    <string name="terms68">1.The cancellation terms are different for each bus operator and are set by the bus operator itself. These terms are shown while booking as well as on the ticket printout/Email confirmation.</string>
    <string name="terms69">2.The cut-off time for canceling a bus ticket depends on either bus start time/boarding point time/bus origin start time. For example: If the bus is scheduled to start from Origin Place at 4 PM and scheduled to reach your en-route selected city at 8 PM and scheduled to reach your selected boarding point at 8:15 PM then the Bus Origin Start Time is 4 PM, Bus Start Time is 8 PM and Boarding Point Time is 8:15 PM.</string>
    <string name="terms70">3.Please read the cancellation terms provided in the search page against each bus service.</string>
    <string name="terms71">4.Tickets booked online should be cancelled online only.</string>
    <string name="terms72">5.Some of the operators accept Partial Cancellation. Please go through the Cancellation Terms in the Ticket.</string>
    <string name="terms73">6.Preponement or Postponement cannot be done once ticket is confirmed.</string>
    <string name="terms74">7.Cancellation of such tickets is not allowed after 15 days from the date of journey.</string>
    <string name="terms75">8.In case of ticket cancellation, Insurance amount is non-refundable.</string>
    <string name="terms76">9.Service Fee/GST are non-refundable for Ticket Cancellation/Service Cancellation</string>
    <string name="terms77">Refunds Policy</string>
    <string name="terms78">By the use of any of the payment method/s available on the DilPay App by You, DilPay shall not be responsible or assume any liability, whatsoever in respect of any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly to You due to any of the following:</string>
    <string name="terms79">1.Lack of authorization for any transaction/s; or</string>
    <string name="terms80">2.Exceeding the preset limit mutually agreed by You and any bank/s; or</string>
    <string name="terms81">3.Any payment issues arising out of the transaction; or</string>
    <string name="terms82">4.Decline of transaction for any other reason/s.</string>
    <string name="terms83">Please note that:</string>
    <string name="terms84">1.Transactions, transaction price and all commercial terms governing the provision of services are bipartite contractual obligations between You and the bus operator. DilPay acts merely as a facilitator being an independent platform and at no point in time, enters into any direct /contractual arrangement with the customers with regard to the services provided by the bus operator. Use of the payment Facility shall not render DiBus liable or responsible for the non-delivery, non-receipt, non-payment, damage, breach of representations and warranties, or fraud as regards the services listed on the Website.</string>
    <string name="terms85">2.You have specifically authorized the app or its service providers to collect, process, facilitate and remit payments and/or the transaction price electronically. Your relationship with app is on a principal to principal basis and by accepting these Terms You agree that Website is an independent contractor for all purposes, and does not have control of or liability for the products or services that are listed on the app that are paid for by using the payment facility.</string>
    <string name="terms86">3.You understand, accept and agree that the payment facility provided through any third party on the app is neither a banking nor financial service provided by DilPay, but is merely a facilitator providing an electronic, automated online electronic payment collection and remittance facility for the Transactions on the app using the existing authorized banking infrastructure and credit card payment gateway networks. Further, by providing payment facility app is neither acting as a trustee nor acting in a fiduciary capacity with respect to the transaction or the transaction price</string>
    <string name="terms87">Governing law and Jurisdiction:</string>
    <string name="terms88">These Terms are governed by and shall be construed in accordance with the laws of India. The courts in Bengaluru shall have exclusive jurisdiction in respect of any disputes arising out of or in connection with these Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms89">Amendment / Modification</string>
    <string name="terms90">DilPay reserves the right to modify these Terms at any time with or without any further notice by uploading the revised Terms on the app and it is Your duty to keep yourself aware of the revisions to the Terms of the app</string>
    <string name="terms91">Disclaimer of Warranties and Liability</string>
    <string name="terms92">1.This app, all the services (including but not limited to software) included on or otherwise made available to You through this Website are provided on "as is" and "as available" basis without any representation or warranties, express or implied except otherwise specified in writing by DilPay or on the app.</string>
    <string name="terms93">2.Without prejudice to the forgoing paragraph, app does not warrant that:</string>
    <string name="terms94">1.app will be constantly available, or available at all; or</string>
    <string name="terms95">2.The information on this app is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading.</string>
    <string name="terms96">3.DilPay will not be liable to You in any way or in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, the app. wherever, the same is under the control of the bus operator. The app does not warrant that this Website; information, content, materials, product (including software) Facility or services included on or otherwise made available to You through the Website; the servers; or electronic communication sent from us are free of viruses or other harmful components, despite our best efforts to prevent these incidents.</string>
    <string name="terms97">4.You are required to enter a valid phone number while booking a bus ticket on the app. By registering Your phone number with us, You consent to be contacted by us for the purposes of the transaction on the app or for sending you promotional offers or content.</string>
    <string name="terms98">5.For the purpose of booking bus tickets through the app, we warrant that we shall be responsible for the following activities:</string>
    <string name="terms99">1.Issuing a valid ticket (a ticket that will be accepted by the bus operator); and</string>
    <string name="terms100">2.Providing customer support and information in case of any delays in the departure of a bus / inconvenience caused to You.</string>
    <string name="terms101">3.DilPay will process the ticket cancellation request from customers subject to the cancellation and refund policy of the respective bus operator. The cancellation fee may differ for each bus operator.</string>
    <string name="terms102">However, We DO NOT take any liability for the following:</string>
    <string name="terms103">1.The bus operators bus not departing from/reaching the pick-up point or destination on time;</string>
    <string name="terms104">2.The bus operators employee/s being rude to You;</string>
    <string name="terms105">3.The bus operators bus seats or the journey not being up to Your expectation;</string>
    <string name="terms106">4.The bus operator modifying and/or cancelling your bus ticket reservation partially or completely due to unavoidable reasons as described in the following clauses;</string>
    <string name="terms107">5.Your baggage getting lost/stolen/damaged;</string>
    <string name="terms108">6.The bus operator changing a customers seat at the last minute to accommodate a female / child passenger;</string>
    <string name="terms109">7.Bus departing without You boarding the bus, while You were waiting at the wrong boarding point (please call the bus operator to find out the exact boarding point if you are not a regular traveller of a particular bus operator);</string>
    <string name="terms110">8.The bus operator changing the boarding point and/or using a pick-up vehicle at the boarding point to take the passengers to the bus departure point; and</string>
    <string name="terms111">9.The bus operator not permitting Your baggage beyond a limit determined at the bus operator sole discretion</string>
    <string name="terms112">Links</string>
    <string name="terms113">1.This app may contain links to other apps maintained by third parties ("External Sites"). These External Sites are linked to the Website for Your reference and convenience only. DilPay does not operate, control or endorse in any respect such External Sites or their content. You assume sole responsibility for use of these External Sites and is therefore, advised to examine the terms and conditions of those External Sites carefully.</string>
    <string name="terms114">2.You must not link Your own app or any third party app, to this app without obtaining the prior written approval of DilPay. Use of any automated screen capture or screen scraping technologies to obtain information from this app without the prior written approval of DilPay is an infringement of our intellectual property rights.</string>
    <string name="terms115">Usage Conduct</string>
    <string name="terms116">1.You acknowledge that You only have a limited right to use the app and that You have no right to modify any part of the Website or reproduce, copy, distribute, sell, resell or access the Facility for any commercial purposes.</string>
    <string name="terms117">2.You are also under an obligation to use this app for reasonable and lawful purposes only, and shall not indulge in any activity that is not envisaged in these Terms. You shall use this app, and any bus tickets purchased through it, for personal, non-commercial use only and shall not re-sell the tickets to any other person.</string>
    <string name="terms118">3.You may not use any meta tags or any other hidden text utilizing the Website or its affiliates names or trademarks without the express written consent of DilPay and or its affiliates, as applicable.</string>
    <string name="terms119">You must not use the Website for any of the following:</string>
    <string name="terms120">1.for fraudulent purposes, or in connection with any criminal acts or other unlawful activity; and/or</string>
    <string name="terms121">2.to send or transport in the carriage of the bus, any material that does not belong to You; or material that is illegal, offensive (including but not limited to material that is sexually explicit content or which promotes racism, bigotry, hatred or physical harm), deceptive, misleading, abusive, indecent, harassing, blasphemous, defamatory, libellous, obscene, pornographic, paedophilic or menacing; ethnically objectionable, disparaging or in breach of copyright, trademark, confidentiality, privacy or any other proprietary information or right; or is otherwise injurious to third parties; or relates to or promotes money laundering or gambling; or is harmful to minors in any way; or impersonates another person; or threatens the unity, integrity, security or sovereignty of India or friendly relations with foreign States; or objectionable or otherwise unlawful in any manner whatsoever; or which consists of or contains software viruses, political campaigning, commercial solicitation, chain letters, mass mailings or any "spam� to cause annoyance, inconvenience or needless anxiety.</string>
    <string name="terms122">Suspension, Termination or Cancellation</string>
    <string name="terms123">App may suspend, cancel or terminate Your account registered with us, with or without prior notice, if we believe in good faith that You have breached any of these Terms or any other terms or policies referred to in these Terms.</string>
    <string name="terms124">DilPay reserves the right, at its sole discretion,to accept, hold and/or cancel any reservation of bus tickets made by the You on the DilPay app, DilPay mobile app and DilPay mobile apps, which is deemed to be fraudu,lent or suspicious by DilPay.</string>
    <string name="terms125">DilPay will endeavour to inform You in the event of cancellation of reservation, owing to fraud or suspicious activity, to the best of its capacity, but shall not be liable for a failure to communicate to You of such cancellation.</string>
    <string name="terms126">Intellectual Property Rights</string>
    <string name="terms127">1.Content included on the Website, such as text, graphics, logos, button icons, images, audio clips, digital downloads, data compilations, and software, is the property of DilPay, its affiliates or its content suppliers and is protected by Indian and international copyright and database right laws.</string>
    <string name="terms128">2.The compilation of all content on this app is the exclusive property of app and its affiliates and is protected by laws of India and international copyright and database right laws. All software used on this app is the property of DilPay, its affiliates or its software suppliers and is protected by Indian and international copyright and authorsrights laws.</string>
    <string name="terms129">3.You may not systematically extract/or re-utilise any parts of the contents of the app without our express written consent. In particular, You may not utilize any data mining, robots, or similar data gathering and extraction tools to extract (whether once or many times) for re-utilisation of any substantial parts of this Website, without DilPays express written consent. You may also not create and/or publish Your own database that features substantial ( eg: prices and service listings) parts of the Website without Rebuss express written consent.</string>
    <string name="terms130">You cannot use the DilPay trademarks for commercially exploiting them for Your interests without our express permission. We reserve the right to initiate legal proceedings if we discover any infringement of our intellectual property rights.</string>
    <string name="terms131">Correspondence/Notices</string>
    <string name="terms132">1.When You use the app or send emails or other data, information or communication to DilPay, You agree and understand that You are communicating with us through electronic records and You consent to receive communications via electronic means from DilPay periodically and as and when required.</string>
    <string name="terms133">2.We may communicate with You through email/SMS or by such other mode of communication, electronic or otherwise.</string>
    <string name="terms134">Payment</string>
    <string name="terms135">1.By the use of any of the payment method/s available on the Website by You, DilPay shall not be responsible or assume any liability, whatsoever in respect of any loss or damage arising directly or indirectly to You due to any of the following:</string>
    <string name="terms136">1.Lack of authorization for any transaction/s; or</string>
    <string name="terms137">2.Exceeding the preset limit mutually agreed by You and any bank/s; or</string>
    <string name="terms138">3.Any payment issues arising out of the transaction; or</string>
    <string name="terms139">4.Decline of transaction for any other reason/s.</string>
    <string name="terms140">2.Please note that</string>
    <string name="terms141">1.Transactions, transaction price and all commercial terms governing the provision of services are bipartite contractual obligations between You and the bus operator. DilPay acts merely as a facilitator being an independent platform and at no point in time, enters into any direct /contractual arrangement with the customers with regard to the services provided by the bus operator. Use of the payment Facility shall not render DilPay liable or responsible for the non-delivery, non-receipt, non-payment, damage, breach of representations and warranties, or fraud as regards the services listed on the app.</string>
    <string name="terms142">2.You have specifically authorized the app or its service providers to collect, process, facilitate and remit payments and/or the transaction price electronically. Your relationship with app is on a principal to principal basis and by accepting these Terms You agree that app is an independent contractor for all purposes, and does not have control of or liability for the products or services that are listed on the app that are paid for by using the payment facility.</string>
    <string name="terms143">3.You understand, accept and agree that the payment facility provided through any third party on the app is neither a banking nor financial service provided by DilPay, but is merely a facilitator providing an electronic, automated online electronic payment collection and remittance facility for the Transactions on the Website using the existing authorized banking infrastructure and credit card payment gateway networks. Further, by providing payment facility Website is neither acting as a trustee nor acting in a fiduciary capacity with respect to the transaction or the transaction price.</string>
    <string name="terms144">Indemnity</string>
    <string name="terms145">1.You shall indemnify and hold harmless DilPay, its subsidiaries, affiliates and their respective officers, directors, agents and employees, from any claim or demand, or actions including reasonable attorneys fees, made by any third party or penalty imposed due to or arising out of Your breach of these Terms or any document incorporated by reference, or Your violation of any law, rules, regulations or the rights of a third party.</string>
    <string name="terms146">2.You hereby expressly release DilPay or any of its affiliates or officers and representatives from any cost, damage, liability or other consequence of any of the actions/inactions of the vendors and specifically waiver any claims or demands that you may have in this behalf under any statute, contract or otherwise.</string>
    <string name="terms147">Carriage Policy</string>
    <string name="terms148">1.You are responsible for ensuring that Your travel date, time and destination are correct before booking/reserving the bus tickets or when you select to confirm your ticket purchase on the app. Please check the cancellation Policy available on the app for details about cancellation and refunds.</string>
    <string name="terms149">2.You are solely responsible to be at the designated boarding point reasonably in advance before departure time. We are not liable if you fail to board the bus by the time the bus departs.</string>
    <string name="terms150">3.The bus operators reserve the right to refuse you and your luggage from carriage on the bus for whatsoever reason that they deem justified, including but not limited to:</string>
    <string name="terms151">1.Carrying of contraband, illegal substances, fragile or oversize/overweight luggage, Your unruly behavior, drunkenness or any other behavior that the bus operator deems to affect the other passengers comfort or safety.</string>
    <string name="terms152">2.You are unable to produce valid government issued identification proof while travelling.</string>
    <string name="terms153">3.The payment of Your fare for the ticket is fraudulent;</string>
    <string name="terms154">4.The booking of Your seat has been done fraudulently or unlawfully or has been purchased from a person not authorized by DilPay;</string>
    <string name="terms155">5.The credit card through which your payment was made for the ticket booking has been reported lost or stolen;</string>
    <string name="terms156">6.The itinerary or booking or confirmation slip is counterfeit or fraudulently obtained;</string>
    <string name="terms157">7.The itinerary of your reservation has been altered by a person other than DilPay or our authorized agent on your express instructions;</string>
    <string name="terms158">8.You are unable to produce a valid and legible boarding ticket for the intended travel. The boarding ticket constitutes as the prima facie evidence of the contract of carriage between the bus operator and the boarding ticket holder;</string>
    <string name="terms159">9.You are deemed medically unfit to travel and may pose a health hazard to other passengers on board the bus, at the absolute discretion of the bus operator;</string>
    <string name="terms160">10.You fail to arrive on time to board before the time of departure or fail to board the bus by the time the bus departs.</string>
    <string name="terms161">11.If the bus operator has refused to carry You or choose to remove You from carriage as per the reasons above mentioned, we reserve the right to cancel the unused ticket and You will not be entitled to further carriage or refund of fare. We will not be liable for the consequential or incidental loss, damage, cost, or fee You may incurdue to the refusal of carriage.</string>
    <string name="terms162">4.Children below age twelve (12) will not be allowed to book tickets for themselves nor will be allowed to travel, unless they are accompanied by an adult.</string>
    <string name="terms163">5.Children above the age of 5 years need to compulsorily obtain a bus ticket at the regular fare of the ticket, unless otherwise a particular bus operator specifies otherwise in their terms and conditions.</string>
    <string name="terms164">6.The bus operator reserve the right to reschedule, cancel, and/or delay any journey and substitute other buses for reasons they deem necessary to do so.</string>
    <string name="terms165">7.You are responsible to ensure that valid and necessary government issued personal identification documents, such as the passport, PAN card or Aadhar card, are carried with you for the journey.</string>
    <string name="terms166">Losses</string>
    <string name="terms167">DilPay will not be responsible for any loss (including loss of profits, revenue, contracts, anticipated savings, data, goodwill or wasted expenditure) and any other indirect or consequential loss to You when You commenced using the app.</string>

    <string name="summary">Use our services &amp; Get percentage to claim your Eligibile Reward Points.</string>
    <string name="mobileRewards">Mobile recharge - 5%</string>
    <string name="defaultRewards">Default rewards - 10%</string>
    <string name="dthRewards">DTH Recharge    - 5%</string>
    <string name="electrictyRewards">Electricity     - 10%</string>
    <string name="gasRewards">Gas		- 5%</string>
    <string name="MoneyRewards">Money Trancefer	- 10%</string>
    <string name="busticketRewards">BusTicket	- 10%</string>
    <string name="referralsRewards">Refferals	-  (1-5%) (2-10%)(3-20%)</string>
    <string name="note">Note: Reward Points will be expired by automatically on 25th of Every Month</string>

<!--    <string name="app_name">Keyguard</string>-->
    <string name="unlock">Unlock</string>
    <string name="confirm_pattern">Confirm your screen lock PIN,Pattern or Password</string>
    <string name="setting_label"><![CDATA[Please set the screen lock Manually by navigating to : Settings>Security.]]></string>
    <string name="unlock_success">App is Unlocked successfully.</string>
    <string name="unlock_failed">Failed to Unlock the app.</string>
    <string name="device_is_secure">Device is now secure.</string>
    <string name="security_device_cancelled">Device is not secure or user cancel the request.</string>
    <string name="authenticate_again">Authenticate Again</string>
</resources>